<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<knimeNode icon="./default.png" type="Source" xmlns="http://knime.org/node/v2.8" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://knime.org/node/v2.10 http://knime.org/node/v2.10.xsd">
    <name>Qvx Writer</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Reads a data table from the input port and produces a Qvx file.
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>
        	<p>
        	Writes Qvx files. Upon executing, the node will read the data table on the in-port. The node
        	will write the appropriate table header information header information for the Qvx file,
        	and then write the data portion of the Qvx file based on the data table.
		  	</p>
        </intro>
        
        <tab name="Settings">
        
        	<option name="Output Location">
        	Enter a valid file name, or select a file from the "Browse" dialog.
        	The supported file format is .qvx.
        	</option>
        	
        	<option name="Table name">
        	Table name of the Qvx file.
        	</option>
        	
        	<option name="If file exists...">
        	Decide whether an existing file should be overwritten on execution, or if execution should
        	be aborted.
        	</option>
    	</tab>
    	
    	<tab name="Field Attributes">
    	
    		<option name="Column Name">
    		Name of the column of the input data table, which will also be the name of the corresponding
    		column in the Qvx file.
    		</option>
    		
    		<option name="Field Attribute">
    		Specifies how QlikView should interpret the data values in the Qvx file.
    		</option>
    		
    		<option name="# Decimals">
    		For the Field Attribute of "FIX", specifies number of decimal places. For the Field Attribute
    		of "REAL", specifies the number of significant digits.
    		</option>
    	</tab>
    	
    	<tab name="Advanced">
    	
    		<option name="Record Separator">
    		Specifies if a record separator byte should be written before each record.
    		</option>
    		
    		<option name="Endianness">
    		Specifies the byte-order of the numerical data values within the Qvx file.
    		</option>
    	</tab>
	</fullDescription>
       
	<ports>
		<inPort index="0" name="Data Table">
		Data table that will be used to generate the Qvx file.
		</inPort>
	</ports>
	
	<views>
		<view index = "0" name = "Settings">
		Choose where the Qvx file will be saved and set whether or not an existing Qvx file should be
		overwritten.
		</view>
		
		<view index = "1" name = "Field Attributes">
		Field Attributes specify how QlikView would interpret the data in the output qvx file. For instance,
		decimal values can be interpreted as money.
		</view>
		
		<view index = "2" name = "Settings">
		Toggle settings that affect the structure of the data in the output Qvx file. These settings
		have no effect on the actual data values that are stored in the Qvx file.
		</view>
	</views>
	
</knimeNode>
